♪ Girls you know you better watch out ♪
♪ Some guys, some guys are only about ♪
♪ That thing, that thing, that thing ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ It's been three weeks ♪
♪ Since you been looking for your friend ♪
♪ The one you let hit it
and never called you again ♪
♪ 'Member when he told you
he was 'bout the Benjamin's ♪
♪ You act like you ain't hear him ♪
♪ Then gave him a little trim ♪
♪ To begin, how you think
you really gon' pretend ♪
♪ Like you wasn't down
then you called him again ♪
♪ Plus when ♪
♪ You give it up so easy
you ain't even foolin' him ♪
♪ If you did it then, then
you'd probably again ♪
♪ Talking out your neck
sayin' you're a Christian ♪
♪ A Muslim sleeping with the gin ♪
♪ Now that was the sin
that did Jezebel in ♪
♪ Who you gon' tell when
the repercussions spin ♪
♪ Showing off your ass 'cause
you're thinking it's a trend ♪
♪ Girlfriend, let me break
it down for you again ♪
♪ You know I only say it
'cause I'm truly genuine ♪
♪ Don't be a hard rock
when you really are a gem ♪
♪ Baby girl, respect is just a minimum ♪
♪ And you still defending 'em now ♪
♪ Lauryn is only human ♪
♪ Don't think I haven't been
through the same predicament ♪
♪ Let it sit inside your
head like a million women ♪
♪ In Philly, Penn ♪
♪ It's silly when girls sell
their soul because it's in ♪
♪ Look at where you be in
hair weaves like Europeans ♪
♪ Fake nails done by Koreans ♪
♪ Come again ♪
♪ Win win come again ♪
♪ Brethren come again ♪
♪ My friend come again ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Guys you know you better watch out ♪
♪ Some girls, some girls are only about ♪
♪ That thing, that thing, that thing ♪
♪ The second verse is
dedicated to the men ♪
♪ More concerned with his rims
and his Timbs than his women ♪
♪ Him and his men come in
the club like hooligans ♪
♪ Don't care who they offend
popping yang like you got yen ♪
♪ Let's not pretend ♪
♪ They wanna pack pistol
by they waist men ♪
♪ Crystal by the case men, still
in they mother's basement ♪
♪ The pretty face men, claiming
that they did a bid men ♪
♪ Need to take care of
their three and four kids ♪
♪ They facing a court case
when the child's support late ♪
♪ Money taking, heart breaking ♪
♪ Now you wonder why women hate men ♪
♪ The sneaky silent men, the
punk domestic violence men ♪
♪ The quick to stop acting
like boys and be men ♪
♪ How you gon' win when
you ain't right within ♪
♪ Uh uh come again ♪
♪ Yo yo come again, brethren come again, ♪
♪ Sistren come again ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Watch out watch out, look out look out ♪
♪ Girls you know you better watch out ♪
♪ Some guys, some guys are only about ♪
♪ That thing, that thing, that thing ♪
♪ Guys you know you better watch out ♪
♪ Cause girls, some girls are only about ♪
♪ That thing, that thing, that thing ♪
♪ Girls you know you better watch out ♪
♪ Some guys, some guys are only about ♪
♪ That thing, that thing, that thing ♪